(Raj:)We're gonna die here.
(Amy:)-Hello.
-Hey.
(Howard:)-Where's Sheldon?
-He's home trying to use science
to determine the basis of humor.
(Bernadette:)-That's interesting.
-It's exhausting.
(Amy:)Do you have any idea how hard it is
(Amy:)to laugh at a knock-knock
joke that starts with,
"Knock-knock-knock, Amy,
knock-knock-knock, Amy,
knock-knock-knock, Amy"?
(Bernadette:)If you want him to stop,
(Bernadette:)sometimes the easiest thing
to do is just fake a laugh.
(Howard:)Fake a laugh?
(Howard:)-Do you ever do that with me?
-No, of course not.
(Howard:)Well, I'd be able to tell anyway.
(Bernadette:)I don't think you would.
(Howard:)Please, I've made
plenty of girls laugh,
(Howard:)sometimes just by
asking them out.